

Andreas Carlsson

Aspiring Developer

Profile

I am a soon to be software developer with a passion for learning. Teamwork, collaboration and bad (read good) humor is corner stones in who I am as a person.

Contact

- **(+46)** 730960702
- ☑ andreas95carlsson@gmail.com
- github.com/AndyCarlsson
- **?** Gothenburg, Sweden

Techstack I have worked with

.NET React Blazor

C# JavaScript HTML CSS

SQL Server MongoDB

GIT

Education

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER .NET

sep 2019 - jun 2021 Newton Yrkeshögskola

This focused education takes place in close collaboration with the industry and includes 24 weeks of internship, divided into two periods. Here is a selection of the courses that I am taking:

- · Object Oriented Programming 1/2
- · Web Development
- Database Technologies
- · Agil Software Development
- Testing
- Entrepreneurship

Digital Media

aug 2014 - jun 2017 | University West

After three years of studies at University West I got my Bachelor of Arts in Informatics by completing courses like:

- · Digital Graphics
- · Web and Interaction Design
- Design Theory
- · User-oriented Design Methodology

Work Experience

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (internship)

sep 2020 - dec 2020 | Plejd

During this 12 week internship I got to be part of a team that built a data visualisation tool from the ground up. My main focus and responsibility was creating a well designed and user friendly front-end. Technologies used was Blazor / C# / html / css.

Serviceman

oct 2018 - aug 2019 Berendsen

As a serviceman at Berendsen my task was to deliver doormats to customers. This was a physical job at its core, but it also required a good servicemind when meeting with customers.